disabledperson.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy • Disabled Person

Please review the following disclaimers carefully before using the disABLEDperson.com site.

### Accessibility

In our continuing effort to increase the functionality of our site, some sections of disABLEDperson.com.com may not be entirely compatible with accepted accessibility standards.

disABLEDperson.com is working to make these sections accessible as quickly as possible. In addition, some of our partners’ sites are not yet Bobby compliant; we are working with our partners to encourage increased accessibility.

If you use an assistive technology that is not compatible with our site or one of our partners’ sites, please email us at disabledpersons@aol.com. disABLEDperson.com welcomes your feedback and hopes that you will be patient with us as we build this community together.

recruitABILITY is a software application that is solely owned by disABLEDperson.com. It’s purpose is to connect our community members with employers looking to hire within our community. disABLEDperson.com is simply acting as a conduit to connect you the disabled individual with a potential employer. Resume posting is free for our community members. disABLEDperson.com expressly disclaims any responsibility or liability for any damage, loss, or injury arising out of a relationship between one of our members and an employer who met on our site. Any difficulties that may arise between a community member and employer that have met on our site is solely between that community member and that employer and both will hold disABLEDperson.com harmless for any liability, damage or loss.

Please check back periodically to be informed of any changes or additions to this policy. We do not anticipate that our philosophy of protecting user information from inappropriate uses and disclosures will change. However, as disABLEDperson.com will be engaged in an ongoing dialogue with private and public bodies (such as TrustE) to ensure that our usage guidelines remain up to date, this policy statement will be modified to reflect refinements, improvements, and changes in our Web site.

### Our Policy

disABLEDperson.com is especially concerned about winning and maintaining the trust of the people in our community. Very often, we hear the question, “Will my privacy be respected?” The answer is a resounding “Yes!” disABLEDperson.com is dedicated not only to advocating on behalf of our community, but also to supporting an individual’s right to have their personal information held in the strictest confidence.

This Web site does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when specifically, knowingly and voluntarily provided by such individuals. A user’s personally identifiable information will not be transferred, sold or loaned to any third party unless otherwise stated at the time of collection.

disABLEDperson.com may use an adult user’s personally identifiable information to deliver to that user alone personalized content, relevant promotional offers and other directed messages. In all such cases, our intent is to better serve our community by providing individual users access to information, products and services that correspond with their personal preferences, expressed interests, or apparent site usage. Individuals have the right to stop their personally identifiable information from being used for such marketing and promotional purposes by sending an e-mail request to us at the address given at the end of this privacy policy. Also, any individual always has the right not to use the disABLEDperson.com Web site and thereby not to receive any directed content at any time.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group. For instance, we might report to potential advertisers that a certain percentage of our users are interested in sports, based on site usage or expressed interests.

disABLEDperson.com may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

It should also be noted that this Web site contains links to other sites. disABLEDperson.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those Web sites.

### Surveys

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). disABLEDperson.com uses contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material targeted to a user’s expressed interests. Contact information may also be used to contact the user when necessary. Users may, however, opt-out of receiving future mailings, as described in the opt-out choice section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. disABLEDperson.com uses this data to tailor our user’s experience at our site, providing targeted information and services. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

### Health

disABLEDperson.com provides health-related information for educational purposes only and is not engaged in rendering medical advice or professional services. The information provided through disABLEDperson.com should not be used for diagnosing or treating a health problem or a disease. It is not a substitute for professional care. If you have or suspect you may have a health problem, you should consult your health care provider.

disABLEDperson.com follows the principles set forth by the Health on the Net Code of Conduct (http://www.hon.ch/HONcode/Conduct_t.html)

  * Any medical/health advice provided and hosted on this site will only be given by medically/health-trained and qualified professionals unless a clear statement is made that a piece of advice offered is from a non-medically/health-qualified individual/organization.
  * The information provided on this site is designed to support, not replace, the relationship that exists between a patient/site visitor and his/her existing physician.
  * The confidentiality of data relating to individual patients and visitors to a medical/health Web site, including their identity, is respected by this Web site.
  * Where appropriate, information contained on this site will be supported by clear references to source data and, where possible, have specific HTML links to that data. The date when a clinical page was last modified will be clearly displayed (e.g. at the bottom of the page).
  * 

Any claims relating to the benefits/performance of a specific treatment, commercial product or

  * service will be supported by appropriate, balanced evidence in the manner outlined above.
  * The designers of this Web site will seek to provide information in the clearest possible manner and provide contact addresses for visitors that seek further information or support.
  * Support for this Web site will be clearly identified, including the identities of commercial and non-commercial organizations that have contributed funding, services, or material for the site.
  * If advertising is a source of funding it will be clearly stated. A brief description of the advertising policy adopted by the Web site owners will be displayed on the site. Advertising and other promotional material will be presented to viewers in a manner and context that facilitates differentiation between it and the original material created by the institution operating the site.

### Cookies

disABLEDperson.com may place a “cookie” in the browser files of the user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifiable information. Although the cookie could enable disABLEDperson.com to relate a user’s use of this site to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided, disABLEDperson.com does not do so except in cases as outlined above, or under an official law enforcement directive.

If you don’t like cookies, your Web browser may include an option that allows you not to accept them. However, we don’t recommend using this option, since it makes browsing our site a less enjoyable and rich experience.

### Kids

If you’re under the age of 18, be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself to anyone over the Internet!

### Parents

disABLEDperson.com assures you that any personally identifiable information collected by this site from children under the age of 18 will not be transferred, sold, or provided to any third party.

disABLEDperson.com should be a place to explore as a family. disABLEDperson.com recommends that adults accompany children when using content on the Internet.

### Opt-Out Choice

Users of our site always have the option not to provide us with personal information. If this information is not shared, however, the user will be denied the opportunity to receive targeted communications and offers from us or our partners. Additionally, if a user wants to remove certain pieces of information from our database so as not to receive future communications or to no longer receive our service altogether, that user can send an email to us at disabledpersons@aol.com asking us to remove that information.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
disABLEDperson.com Inc.  
PO Box 230636  
Encinitas Ca. 92023-0636
